asuswebstorage.com 2015-03-15

# Online backup, file sync, for pad, PC, Android and iPhone - ASUS WebStorage

ASUS Cloud Corporation (hereinafter referred to as “ASUS Cloud,” “We,” or “US”) Privacy Protection Policy (hereinafter referred to as “Privacy Protection Policy”) outlines what personal information we may collect, how we use and safeguard the collected personal information and with whom we may share it. Your submission of your personal information to ASUS Cloud will be deemed that you accept the Privacy Protection Policy.

#### Information That ASUS Cloud Collect and How ASUS Cloud Use It

You acknowledge and agree that we acquire your personal data, such as name, post address (including post code), nickname, email address, telephone, fax number, and other relevant identification as required for the purpose of providing services. We will acquire your personal data under the following circumstances, including but not limited to:

  1. We will preserve the system- generated records when you browse or search through our website. These records include your IP address, IP addresses of your network infrastructure, duration of using our services, your web browser, visited web pages and links and etc. We will tag different browsers used by individual connections, conclude visited pages in our website by different web browsers, and analyze the cumulative behavior of all users. We do not analyze specific behavior of an individual user.
  2. The data acquired by ASUS Cloud will only be used for commercial and marketing analyses; We will not use these data for any other purpose or disclose any personal data without your prior consent.

For such purposes as mentioned above portions of your personal information may be transferred to our agents and/or contractors acting on our behalf and within the scope of the purposes, and we will ensure that those agents and/or contractors are strictly in compliance with the Privacy Protection Policy.

We will not use or transfer to third parties your personal information for any unrelated purposes, unless and to the extent it is required by applicable laws or regulations or the competent governmental or judicial authorities, necessary to establish or preserve a legal claim or defense, or necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.

We will in particular not sell or market your personal information to any third parties.

We will cease using your personal information held by us once the personal information is no longer required for ASUS to carry out the purpose for which the personal information was intended to be used.

In order to protect users' privacy, we do not provide any service to inquire the account and information of other users. For legal problems which require inquiry of another user's information, please contact police departments or law enforcing units.

You acknowledge and agree that We may send you commercially-related materials or emails. We will provide instructions and contacts on how to stop receiving these materials or emails.

When you submit personal information to Asus Cloud, you understand and agree that this personal information may be transferred between ASUS Cloud offices and agents and/or contractors of ASUS Cloud internationally, and may be stored and processed in any of the countries which ASUS Cloud offices and agents and/or contractors of ASUS Cloud locate in. All transfer, storage and use of your personal information shall be subject to and protected by the Privacy Protection Policy.

#### If your account is managed by an administrator

Your administrator may be able to: 

  1. Change your account password
  2. Suspend or terminate your account access
  3. Access or retain information stored as part of your account
  4. Receive your account information in order to satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request
  5. Restrict your ability to delete or edit information or privacy settings

#### How You Can Access Your Information

YOU may query, view, archive, amend and correct YOUR registration information by logging in and editing YOUR account settings on OUR web site.

You can email technical support service of ASUS Cloud at contact@asuswebstorage.com to request us cease collecting, process and using your personal information or delete and remove your registered account.

#### Additional Information Concerning Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children without their parent’s or guardian’s consent. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests while using the service. If you are a child, please seek and verify your parent’s or guardian’s consent. Only after we verify your parent’s or guardian’s consent, you may submit personal information to us. Your parent or guardian can revoke any consent previously given.

#### Sensitive Personal Information

ASUS Cloud will never ask you to provide sensitive personal information such as information about your medical or health record, political or religious beliefs, criminal offences alleged or committed criminal conviction background, sexual orientation, sexual life or genetic information. Please refrain from providing us with such information.

#### Security

We take precautions to protect your personal information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. These include internal reviews of our personal information collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store your personal information. Transmission of personal information between different locations of ASUS Cloud affiliated companies is performed through our secured wide area network. When you submit personal information via the service, your information is protected both online and offline. However, ASUS Cloud cannot guarantee a perfect security on the internet. When using the internet, we recommended that you use alphanumerical usernames and passwords and change your passwords on a regular basis, as well as keep your computer up to date by applying the latest available security updates for your software and using such tools as virus/spyware scanners.

If you have any questions regarding the security of our web site, please refer to our security web page.

#### Amendment of Privacy Protection Policy

You acknowledge and agree that We reserve the right to amend or change our Privacy Protection Policy. We will make our Privacy Protection Policy amendment or change notice in this web page; and for material amendment and change to our Privacy Protection Policy. Official notification will be released via email to you or on our website (www.asuswebstorage.com) whenever there is major amendment for our policy of utilizing personal data. Your continuing use of the service will be deemed your acknowledgement and agreement to our policy as amended.

#### Contacting Us

If you have any inquiries, questions, comments or complaints about the Privacy Protection Policy, please feel free to contact us at contact@asuswebstorage.com.

Updated September 2, 2014 by ASUS Cloud Corporation
